Guide to the African Collection, Yale University Library, Records of the Curator
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Administrative records of the curator of the African Collection, 1979-2013; Accession 2015-A-011
  - Artists for a new South Africa, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Asylum cases, 2006-2008 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Cadbury collection, 2000-2012 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Karis/Gerhart, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Katjavivi papers, 1989-2000 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Kenya project, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Manuscripts-purchases, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Mercy archive, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Oversize materials
    - Posters, Undated, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Pogrund, Benjamin, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Rights and Wrongs, 1993-2003 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - South Africa Now, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Schechter, Danny/South Africa Now, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Sylvia Boone papers, 2001-2010 (Box 1, Folder 32)